Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXXIII is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XXXIV is arranged in 35 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXXIII. COMMITTEE FOR INTERNATIONAL ECONOMIC GROWTH
  - Sub-Series 264-0. Committee for International Economic Growth
    - General, 1958-1959 (Box 224, Folder 22)
- Series XXXIV. CONFERENCES
  - Sub-Series 269-0. Conferences
    - Conference for Progressive Political Action, 1924 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 269-1. Conferences
    - Proposed Conference of Governors of the New England States, 1921 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - Annual Conference on Organization: Grand Lodge Officers, General Chairmen, et. al., 1962 (Box 225, Folder 3-6)
      November 27-29, 1962.
    - National Organization Conference. Minutes, 1961 (Box 225, Folder 7-9)
      May 2-4, 1961.
    - National Organization Conference. Grand Lodge Officers, General Chairmen, et. al., 1961 (Box 225, Folder 10)
    - National Conference on Organization. Minutes, 1960 (Box 225, Folder 11-12)
      June 14-16, 1960.
    - National Conference on Organization. Grand Lodge Officers, General Chairmen, et. al., 1960 (Box 225, Folder 13)
    - National Conference on Legislation. Grand Lodge Officers, General Chairmen, et. al., 1959 (Box 225, Folder 14-19)
      November 9-11, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 269-2. Conferences
    - Conference with President of American Federation of Labor, Washington, 1933 (Box 225, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 269-3. Conferences
    - Conference of General Chairmen. Expense Accounts, 1921 (Box 225, Folder 21)
      1921 April
  - Sub-Series 269-4. Conferences
    - Meetings of Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1934 (Box 226, Folder 1)
      December 5-6, 1934.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1934 (Box 226, Folder 2)
      August 1, 1934-September 11, 1934.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1934 (Box 226, Folder 3)
      January 1, 1934-July 31, 1934.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Chicago Dinner, 1933-1934 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1933 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1933 (Box 226, Folder 6)
      April 28-29, 1933.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1932 (Box 226, Folder 7-8)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1931 (Box 226, Folder 9)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1931 (Box 226, Folder 10)
      December 9-11, 1931.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1930 (Box 226, Folder 11)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1929 (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1928 (Box 226a, Folder 1)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1926-1927 (Box 226a, Folder 2)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1923-1925 (Box 226a, Folder 3)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1922 (Box 226a, Folder 4)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1939 (Box 226a, Folder 5)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1938 (Box 226a, Folder 6)
      August 17, 1938-December 1938.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1938 (Box 226a, Folder 7)
      January 1938-August 16, 1938.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1937 (Box 226a, Folder 8)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1936 (Box 226a, Folder 9)
      April-December 1936.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1936 (Box 226a, Folder 10)
      January-April 1936.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1937-1938 (Box 226a, Folder 11)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1935-1936 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1935 (Box 227, Folder 2)
      July-December 1935.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1935 (Box 227, Folder 3)
      January-June 1935.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1944 (Box 227, Folder 4)
      June-December 1944.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1944 (Box 227, Folder 5)
      February-May 1944.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1943-1945 (Box 227, Folder 6)
      November 1943-April 1945.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1943 (Box 227, Folder 7)
      September-December 1943.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1943 (Box 227, Folder 8)
      January-August 1943.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1942-1943 (Box 227, Folder 9)
      November 1942-October 1943.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1942 (Box 228, Folder 1)
      July-December 1942.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1942 (Box 228, Folder 2)
      January-June 1942.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1941-1942 (Box 228, Folder 3)
      January 1941-October 1942.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1941 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1940 (Box 228, Folder 5)
      June 27, 1940-December 1940.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1939-1940 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1940 (Box 228, Folder 7)
      January 1940-June 5, 1940.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1948-1949 (Box 228, Folder 8)
      October 1948-March 22, 1949.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1947-1948 (Box 228, Folder 9)
      December 1947-March 1948.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Financial Statements, 1948-1951 (Box 228, Folder 10)
      May 1948-51.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1948 (Box 229, Folder 1)
      April-September 1948.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Dinner in honor of T.C. Cashen, 1947 (Box 229, Folder 2)
      1947 November 12
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Dinner in honor of B.M. Jewell, 1946 (Box 229, Folder 3)
      1946 June 27
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 229, Folder 4)
      December 1947-48.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1946-1947 (Box 229, Folder 5)
      August 1946-November 1947.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1947 (Box 229, Folder 6)
      May-November 1947.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1946-1947 (Box 229, Folder 7)
      December 1946-April 1947.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1946 (Box 229, Folder 8)
      April-November 1946.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Financial Statements, 1943-1948 (Box 229, Folder 9)
      1943-April 1948.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 229, Folder 10)
      1945-July 1946.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1945-1946 (Box 229, Folder 11)
      October 1945-March 1946.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1945 (Box 229, Folder 12)
      May-September 1945.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 229, Folder 13)
      1955-February 1956.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1956 (Box 229, Folder 14)
      February 10, 1956-October 13, 1956.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes. March 1956-August 11, 1956 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1955-1956 (Box 230, Folder 2)
      October 1955-February 9, 1956.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1954-1955 (Box 230, Folder 3)
      November 1954-September 1955.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 230, Folder 4)
      September 1953-October 1954.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 230, Folder 5)
      August 1953-54.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1952-1953 (Box 230, Folder 6)
      March 1952-August 1953.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 230, Folder 7)
      1952-July 1953.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1951-1952 (Box 230, Folder 8)
      June 1951-February 1952.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1951 (Box 230, Folder 9)
      February-December 1951.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes. March 1950-January 1951 (Box 230, Folder 10)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 230, Folder 11)
      1949-February 1950.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1950-1951 (Box 230, Folder 12)
      October 1950-May 1951.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1950 (Box 231, Folder 1)
      April 16, 1950-September 1950.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1949-1950 (Box 231, Folder 2)
      December 1949-April 15, 1950.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Conference of Railroad Presidents, 1949-1950 (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1949 (Box 231, Folder 4)
      June-November 1949.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1949 (Box 231, Folder 5)
      March 23, 1949-May 1949.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Special Report to the Governor on Problems of the Railroads and Bus Lines in New York State, 1959 (Box 231, Folder 6)
      1959 March 12
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Conference, Commuter Situation, New York Metropolitan Area, 1959 (Box 231, Folder 7)
      1959 March 5
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Railway Passenger Service Dissertation. June 1959 (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. News, 1958-1959 (Box 231, Folder 9)
      1958-August 1959.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1958 (Box 231, Folder 10)
      July 8, 1958-November 1958.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1957-1958 (Box 231, Folder 11)
      December 1957-July 7, 1958.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1957 (Box 231, Folder 12)
      June-November 1957.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1958 (Box 231, Folder 13)
      July-December 1958.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes. March-June 1958 (Box 231, Folder 14)
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 232, Folder 1)
      August 1957-February 1958.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1957 (Box 232, Folder 2)
      April-July 1957.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association. Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 232, Folder 3)
      August 12, 1956-March 1957.
    - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1956-1957 (Box 232, Folder 4)
      October 14, 1956-May 1957.
  - Sub-Series 269-5. Conferences
    - Railway Employees' Department, American Federation of Labor, 1921-1922 (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - Railway Employees' Department, American Federation of Labor, 1921-1922 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 269-6. Conferences
    - Meeting of General Chairmen, 1921 (Box 232, Folder 7)
      1921 July
  - Sub-Series 269-7. Conferences
    - Unemployment Conference, 1921 (Box 232, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 269-8. Conferences
    - National Council for Prevention of War, 1921-1923 (Box 232, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 269-9. Conferences
    - Chicago Conference of General Chairmen, 1921 (Box 232, Folder 10)
      1921 October, 23
  - Sub-Series 269-10. Conferences
    - Conference of Progressives, 1931 (Box 232, Folder 11)
    - National Progressive Conference, 1925 (Box 232, Folder 12)
    - National Progressive Conference, 1924 (Box 232, Folder 13)
    - Conference for Progressive Political Action, 1924 (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Conference for Progressive Political Action, 1924 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Conference for Progressive Political Action, 1923 (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Conference for Progressive Political Action, 1922 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 269-11. Conferences
    - Hoover Conference, 1922 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 269-12. Conferences
    - Conference of Central Labor Unions of Ohio, 1923 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 269-13. Conferences
    - Conference of Trade Union Legislative Representatives, 1923 (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 269-14. Conferences
    - Conference of General Chairmen, 1924 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 269-15. Conferences
    - Conference of General Chairmen, 1926 (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 269-16. Conferences
    - Conference of Certain General Chairmen and Others. Expense Accounts, 1925 (Box 233, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 269-17. Conferences
    - Conference of General Chairmen, 1926 (Box 233, Folder 11)
      1926 January 11
  - Sub-Series 269-18. Conferences
    - Conference of Express General Chairmen, 1928 (Box 233, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 269-19. Conferences
    - Research and Statistical Bureau, 1930-1931 (Box 233, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 269-20. Conferences
    - Organization Conference, 1930-1931 (Box 233, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 269-21. Conferences
    - Unemployment Conference held by Governor Murray of Oklahoma, 1931 (Box 233, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 269-22. Conferences
    - Third Annual Organization Conference, 1932 (Box 233, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 269-23. Conferences
    - National Conference of Grand Lodge Officers and General Chairmen, 1933 (Box 233, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 269-24. Conferences
    - Fourth Annual Organization Conference, 1934 (Box 233, Folder 18-19)
      November 13-14, 1934.
  - Sub-Series 269-25. Conferences
    - Meeting of Grand Lodge and System Board Officers Standard Railroad Labor Organization, 1935 (Box 233, Folder 20)
      1935 January 12
  - Sub-Series 269-26. Conferences
    - Fifth Annual Organization Conference, 1935 (Box 233, Folder 21)
    - Annual Organization Conferences. Minutes, 1929-1936 (Box 233, Folder 22)
    - Annual Organization Conferences. Minutes, 1937-1939 (Box 233, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 269-27. Conferences
    - National Organization Conference, 1936-1937 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 269-28. Conferences
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1936-1937 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 269-29. Conferences
    - National Organization Conference, 1938 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Eighth Annual Conference on Organization. Minutes, 1938 (Box 234, Folder 4)
      December 15-16, 1938.
  - Sub-Series 269-30. Conferences
    - Ninth Annual Conference on Organization. Minutes, 1939 (Box 234, Folder 5)
      November 6-9, 1939.
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1939 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Regional and Educational Meeting, 1939 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - Annual Organization Conferences. Minutes, 1941-1942 (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 269-31. Conferences
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1939 (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - Tenth Annual Conference on Organization. Minutes, 1941 (Box 234, Folder 10)
      January 28-30, 1941.
  - Sub-Series 269-32. Conferences
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1941-1942 (Box 234, Folder 11)
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 12)
    - Eleventh Annual Conference on Organization. Minutes, 1942 (Box 234, Folder 13)
      1942 July 14
  - Sub-Series 269-33. Conferences
    - Annual Organization Conferences, 1943-1946 (Box 234, Folder 14)
      1943-November 1946.
    - National Organization Conference, 1950 (Box 234, Folder 15)
      1950 May 24
    - National Organization Conference, 1949-1950 (Box 234, Folder 16)
      1949-May 23, 1950.
    - National Organization Conferences. Minutes, 1950 (Box 234, Folder 17-18)
      April 24-28, 1950.
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1948-1949 (Box 234, Folder 19)
      March 1948-49.
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1947-1948 (Box 234, Folder 20)
      February 1947-February 1948.
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1948 (Box 235, Folder 1)
      February 4-6, 1948.
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1946-1947 (Box 235, Folder 2)
      December 1946-January 1947.
  - Sub-Series 269-34. Conferences
    - Conference on Organization, 1958 (Box 235, Folder 3-6)
      April 1-4, 1958.
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1957 (Box 235, Folder 7-9)
      March 28-30, 1957.
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1956 (Box 235, Folder 12-13)
      February 28-March 2, 1956.
    - Conference of General Chairmen, 1955 (Box 235, Folder 14-15)
      February 23-25, 1955.
    - National Organization Conference, 1954 (Box 235, Folder 16-17)
      April 13-15, 1954.
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1953 (Box 235, Folder 18)
      July 27-28, 1953.
    - General Chairmen's Conference, 1950 (Box 235, Folder 19)
      November 16-18, 1950.